# **AUSTIN DREOSCH**

## SOFTWARE ENGINEER

**(** 707-308-9486

austindreosch@gmail.com

San Francisco Bay Area, CA

Full-stack developer with 6+ years of independent project experience coupled with a comprehensive formal education in software engineering and a bachelors degree from Sonoma State University. Expertise spanning multiple languages, toolsets and paradigms. My defining quality is an endless curiosity and passion for learning, which has driven my success in my education. Exceptional soft-skills candidate and generous communicator with a bright spirited ambitious temperament.

## EDUCATION



#### **Software Engineering**

2022 - 2024

Springboard | San Francisco, CA

Intensive hands-on experience in end-to-end software development principles in multiple programming languages (JavaScript, Python, C#) with technical skills focused on full stack web applications in emerging technologies, data structures & algorithms, asynchronous dynamic programming, APIs, testing & C.S. fundamentals.



#### General Studies, Bachelor's

2017 - 2021

Sonoma State University | Rohnert Park, CA

Graduated with my Bachelor's in a broad multidisciplinary program focused around critical thinking, mathematics, art, science, literature, communication, and problem solving.

#### SKILLS

















Firebase



React









Express







#### **EXPERIENCE**



## Marketing / Design

Mar 2023 - Present

Engel & Völkers | St. Helena, CA

- Led development and design of all marketing and client presentations for top Napa real estate agent with annual sales volume exceeding \$200,000,000.
- Operated in leadership role with junior employees, interns heading team collaboration and office management.



### **Workplace Coordinator**

Mar 2022 - Jan 2023

CBRE | Austin, TX

- · Managed all employee-facing services & communication between clients, vendors, staff in Austin for the world's largest commercial real estate firm.
- Contributed in the production and implementation of marketing materials and branded campaigns.







GitHub ⊘

## **PROJECTS**



# Playbook Al

Web |

GitHub ⊘



Fantasy sports analyzer with external team imports. Organized sports data visualization with multiple data streams demonstrating complex API manipulation and NoSQL database solution.

JavaScript

Next.js

MongoDB

authO

Tailwind

OpenAl



#### **Quillwind Al**

Web |



GitHub €



Generative AI solution for producing SEO optimized blog pieces through integration with OpenAI API. SAAS web app functionality with Stripe integration and secure user authentication with authO.

JavaScript

React

**OpenAl** 

MongoDB

auth0



# **Prep Kitchen**



Meal delivery service app demonstration full-stack Python development with the SQLAlchemy ORM and integration of the MealDB API. Made with custom CSS and jQuery.





PostgreSQL





